# JI YEON LEE

DESIGNER

917.834.4686



jiylee89@gmail.com



Edgewater, New Jersey



Jiyeonlee1011

#### EDUCATION

## SOUTHERN NEW HAMPSHIRE UNIVERSITY

Candidate for Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design and Media Arts / Web Design

2020 - 2022

# FASHION INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Arts in Fashion Design / Knitwear Design

2010 - 2014

### SKILLS

#### Software

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Animate Lightroom HTML/CSS

#### Design

Design Research
Design Strategy
User Interface
Web Design
Video Editing
Photo Editing

#### ABOUT ME

I'm a designer based in New York City. I've been working as Womenswear designer with many companies of all sizes to create beautiful products over 5 years. In design, I value simplicity, beauty and craftsmanship, always seeking to create work that balances modern and classic aesthetics. I have a particular interest in branding, editorial, print design, web design, and UI/UX design.

I am a graduate of the Fashion Institute of Technology and pursuing Bachelor of Arts degree in graphic deisgn at Southern New Hampshire University.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Woven/Cut & Sew Knit Designer

Juven's, Inc. | July 2017-Sept 2019: Women's Violet + Claire/Printemps

Led design team for Printemps Spring 2020 Collection.

Researched and developed cut & sew knits for Violet + Claire Spring 2020 Collection.

- Responsible for sketching, trimming and tech pack completion of full collection
- Directed styling at e-commerce photo shoot sessions
- Organized and participated in bi weekly fittings to achieve top fit and quality
- Created cad works for print placements and detailed tech packs
- Provided supervision and support for associate and assistant designers

#### Associate Woven Designer

Juven's, Inc.| July 2015-Jun 2017: Women's Violet + Claire

Designed, researched and developed monthly deliveries. Clients include T.J. Maxx, Dress Barn, Century 21, Laurie Felt, and Winners.

- Responsible for making trim chart, checking sample yardage and proceed lab dips
- Developed flat sketches using illustrator

#### INTERNSHIPS

TORY BURCH | Feb 2014-May 2014: Knitwear Design Intern MICHAEL KORS | Sep 2013-Dec 2013: Knitwear Design Intern OSCAR DE LA RENTA | May 2013-Dec 2013: Fur Design Intern BRANDON SUN | May 2013-Dec 2013: Woven Design Intern